hi folks this is Matt here to tell you a
大家好，我是马特，在这里告诉您
little bit more about Bayesian games so
关于贝叶斯游戏的更多信息
we're going to take a look at a quick
我们将快速浏览
example just to illustrate some of the
这个例子只是为了说明一些
concepts and to see at least in a simple
概念，至少要看一个简单
example how you might think about
示例您可能会如何思考
solving one of these games and what
解决其中一种游戏以及什么
later in the course we'll be talking a
在课程的后面，我们将讨论
little bit more about auctions so you'll
有关拍卖的更多信息，您将
have a chance to look at look at some
有机会看一下
auctions as well okay
拍卖也可以
Bayesian Nash equilibrium what did it do
贝叶斯纳什均衡它做了什么
again it has a plan of action for every
再次有一个针对每个人的行动计划
player so we have what they're going to
玩家，所以我们有他们要做什么
do as a function of their information
根据他们的信息来做
their types and it's maximizing your
他们的类型，这是最大化您的
expected utility expecting over what
期望效用
they think other players are going to be
他们认为其他玩家将会
doing and expecting over the types of
做和期待的类型
other players which might affect their
其他可能影响他们的球员
payoff so let's took it a very simple
回报，所以让我们非常简单
example so this is a sort of a
例如，这是一种
hollywood-style example so let's call it
好莱坞风格的例子，让我们称之为
the sheriff's dilemma so this is a very
警长的困境，所以这是一个非常
simple setting where you've got a
简单的设置，您可以在其中
sheriff and they're faced with an armed
警长，他们面对武装
suspect imagine they've both pulled guns
怀疑他们俩都拉了枪
and they're standing there staring at
他们站在那儿凝视着
each other with their guns in hand and
彼此拿着枪
they have to decide whether to shoot at
他们必须决定是否在
the other or not and we know we could do
对方与否，我们知道我们可以做
this in a Wild West we could do it in a
在狂野西部，我们可以在
cop thriller etc but the idea is you're
警察惊悚片等，但想法是你是
faced with this dilemma do you shoot or
面对这个难题，您会射击还是
not when when you're faced with the
不是当你面对
armed suspect and in this case let's
武装嫌疑犯，在这种情况下，让我们
suppose that the suspect is either a
假设嫌疑人是
criminal with probability P or not with
有或没有
probability one minus P so either
概率一减去P，所以
they're guilty of some crime or they're
他们犯了一些罪或者他们
innocent and in particular when we think
天真，尤其是当我们认为
about this the sheriff would rather not
对此，警长宁愿不要
shoot well you rather shoot if the
拍摄好你宁愿射击如果
suspects going to shoot so if you're
怀疑会射击，所以如果你是
going to get shot at you want to defend
要为你的防守而开枪
yourself but you would rather not shoot
你自己，但你宁愿不射击
if the suspect is not even if it's a
如果嫌疑人不是，即使是
criminal or not you don't want to shoot
罪犯与否，你不想开枪
the person if they're not going to shoot
如果他们不射击的人
you if it's a criminal you'd rather take
如果你是罪犯，你宁愿带走
them to jail if it's if it's a innocent
如果是无辜的话，他们就入狱
person you'd rather not shoot them at
你不想开枪的人
all so the sheriff would rather not
所以警长宁愿不要
shoot if the if it's suspect doesn't but
如果怀疑，则进行拍摄
will defend themselves a shot at and the
会为自己辩护，
criminal would rather shoot even if the
罪犯宁愿开枪，即使
sheriff does not so this is a situation
警长不这样，这是一种情况
where if they they'll realize they're
如果他们会意识到他们在哪里
going to be caught if they don't shoot
如果他们不射击就会被抓住
and and so they're going to want to
因此，他们将要
shoot and the UNICEF suspect would
射击，联合国儿童基金会的嫌疑人会
rather not shoot even if the sheriff
即使警长也不射击
shoots at them because they realize if
向他们开枪，因为他们意识到
the sheriff ends up shooting they're
警长最终开枪他们是
going to die
快死了
maybe they'd rather not shoot and be
也许他们宁愿不射击而成为
remembered for shooting the sheriff so
记得因射击警长而死
so that's the setting of the game very
所以这就是游戏的设置
simply let's take a look at possible
简单地让我们看一下可能
payoffs and the structure of this so
收益及其结构
let's have the sheriff be the column
让警长成为专栏
player so they can shoot or not and here
球员，所以他们可以射击与否，在这里
in terms of the representation we can
在代表性方面，我们可以
think of there's two different types of
想想有两种不同类型的
the player there's this theta for the
玩家有这个theta
innocent suspect and theta for the
无辜的嫌疑人和theta
guilty suspect so it could either be the
有罪嫌疑人，所以它可能是
bad or a good suspect and this is
好或坏的嫌疑犯，这是
happening with so the innocence is
发生这样的天真是
happening with a probability 1 minus P
发生概率为1减去P
and the guilty is happening with a
而罪恶正在发生
probability P so this probability P
概率P所以这个概率P
you've got this guilty 1 1 minus P on
你有罪恶感1 1减去P
the innocent and the sheriff doesn't
无辜的警长不
know what the type of the individual is
知道个人的类型是什么
the suspect is ok so then we've got
嫌疑犯还可以，所以我们得到了
payoffs in here and the payoffs reflect
这里的收益和收益反映
the basic structure that we talked about
我们讨论的基本结构
before so in particular you know if if
尤其是在此之前，您是否知道
you're if you're going to be shot at if
你是如果你会被枪杀
the the sheriff is going to be shot at
警长将被开枪
they're going to get a better payoff
他们将获得更好的回报
from shooting the knot in either case
在任何情况下都不会打结
they'd rather you know it's a negative
他们希望您知道这是负面的
payoff here so so actually if you don't
在这里得到回报，所以实际上如果您不这样做
shoot in there shooting you that's a bad
射在那射击你真不好
payoff you're going to get killed
回报，你会被杀死
if you shoot back you might end up
如果你回头，你可能会失败
hurting a person in this in this case
在这种情况下伤害一个人
you know they're getting a negative
你知道他们越来越消极
payoff because they're actually shooting
回报，因为他们实际上是在射击
innocent individual and so forth so it's
无辜的个人等等
you know you know then not not here is
你知道你知道然后不是这里不是
the best payoff for these individuals
这些人的最佳回报
for the when they're looking at a
当他们看着一个
criminal the guilty / individual again
再犯有罪/个人
they'd rather shoot if the criminal is
他们宁愿开枪，如果罪犯是
going to shoot they
要拍摄他们
in the case where the criminal does not
如果罪犯没有
they would get a payoff of one from
他们将从中得到一个回报
actually capturing a criminal and taking
实际上抓捕罪犯并采取
them away and so forth so we've got
他们离开等等，所以我们有
payoffs that we can look at and you can
我们可以看到的收益，您可以
study this in a little more detail and
对此进行更详细的研究，
then the question is what what's
那么问题是什么
actually going to happen in terms of the
实际上将发生在
play of this game okay so what we can do
玩这个游戏好吧，我们该怎么办
is begin to analyze okay if we're faced
开始分析，如果我们面对的话
with the good suspect the innocent one
与好嫌疑人无辜
then what are they going to do
那他们该怎么办
so let's first try and calculate what
所以我们先尝试计算一下
the suspect is going to do and what we
嫌疑人将要做什么，我们该怎么办
see here is that the suspect in this
看到这里是嫌疑犯
particular situation conditional once
有条件的一次特殊情况
they see their type of being good then
他们看到自己的类型很好
they should end up here they get a
他们应该在这里结束他们得到一个
payoff of minus one if they shoot zero
如果他们拍摄零，则收益为负一
if they don't so they'd rather not shoot
如果他们不这样做，他们宁愿不射击
here they get a minus three if they
如果他们在这里得到负三
shoot a minus two if they don't so we
如果他们不拍负两
end up with a strictly dominant strategy
最终采取严格的主导策略
of not shooting if you're good so
如果你很好就不要开枪
essentially what that tells us is that
本质上告诉我们的是
if we're looking at for Beijing
如果我们在寻找北京
equilibrium the good player regardless
平衡好球员，无论
of what they think the sheriff should do
他们认为警长应该做什么
should not shoot right so we can cross
不应该射击正确，所以我们可以穿越
this out and say that the only possible
说出来，这是唯一可能的
strategy for a good player is that
优秀球员的策略是
they're not going to shoot okay now we
他们现在不会开枪了，我们
go to the bad player and we do a similar
去找坏人，我们做类似的事情
kind of calculation and basically the
一种计算，基本上
criminal is going to shoot in this case
在这种情况下，罪犯将开枪
right so we look the zero vs minus two
正确，所以我们看零与负二
two versus one the this shoot strictly
严格来说，这是两对一
dominates not for the bad player once
一次不为坏玩家统治
they know their type so that tells us
他们知道他们的类型，这告诉我们
that in in terms of either an interim
就临时而言
plan or even if we go back ex ante and
计划，甚至我们事前回去
try and figure out what these players
尝试找出这些球员
should do basically the good one should
应该基本上做的好
not shoot and the bad one should shoot
不射击，坏人应该射击
and so now we've got a probability P
所以现在我们有概率P
down here 1 minus P here and we want to
在这里1减去P在这里，我们想
ask what's the sheriff's best reply okay
问警长最好的答复是什么好
well basically what happens if they
好吧，如果他们会发生什么
shoot what are they going to get they
拍摄他们将要得到什么
get 0 down here the sheriff gets a minus
警长减为零
1 up here so you're getting minus 1
在这里1，所以你得到负1
times 1 minus P if they shoot if they
如果他们射击，则乘以1减去P
don't shoot what do they get
不要射击他们会得到什么
if they don't shoot well they get zero
如果射击不好，他们将得到零
up here and minus two down here so they
在这里，减去两个在这里，所以他们
get a minus two times P and so we can
减去P的两倍，所以我们可以
think of the situations when is it
想想什么时候
better to shoot when is it better not to
最好在什么时候拍摄更好
and you can check here that if P is
你可以在这里检查P是否为
greater than one-third right so if you
大于三分之一的权利，所以如果你
find that point where these two are
找到这两个在哪里
exactly equal to each other that's going
彼此完全相等
to be the point where P is equal to 1/3
是P等于1/3的点
if P is bigger than 1/3 then you're more
如果P大于1/3，则您更大
likely to be down here you're more
可能会在这里你更多
likely to want to shoot and if P is less
可能想拍摄，如果P小于
than 1/3 then you would want to not so
超过1/3，那么您可能会不想那样
depending on what P is you're going to
取决于您要使用的P
have bayesian equilibria so the Bayesian
有贝叶斯均衡，所以贝叶斯
equilibria of this game are going to be
这个游戏的平衡点将会是
for the the good type or sorry the
对于好的类型或对不起
innocent type I guess innocent type here
我想这里是无辜的类型
should always not shoot the guilty type
永远不要开枪认罪
should always end up shooting and then
应该总是结束射击然后
the sheriff if P is greater than
如果P大于
one-third the sheriff shoots P is less
警长射击的三分之一P小于
than 1/3 they do not and for P equals
大于1/3则不等于P
1/3 any mixture for the sheriff the
1/3警长的任何混合物
sheriff can just flip a coin they're
警长可以掷硬币
completely indifferent between shooting
拍摄之间完全无所谓
and not when P is exactly 1/3 so we have
而不是当P恰好是1/3时
a Bayesian equilibrium in this case the
在这种情况下的贝叶斯均衡
Bayesian equilibrium is going to be
贝叶斯均衡将是
generically unique it's going to be
一般而言，它将是唯一的
unique as long as P is not 1/3 and
只要P不为1/3并且不唯一
whether or not they decide to shoot
他们是否决定射击
depends on what their payoffs are and so
取决于他们的收益是什么
what one thing that this this example
这个例子有什么一件事
illustrates for it's a fairly simple
举例说明，这很简单
example but it still captures the basic
例子，但它仍然捕获了基本的
elements of Bayesian equilibrium how so
贝叶斯均衡的要素如何
well there's several things going on
好吧，发生了几件事
first is that the payoffs of both
首先是两者的收益
players depend on what the type is ok so
玩家取决于哪种类型还可以，所以
whether the sheriff is getting a higher
警长是否越来越高
low payoff from shooting or not exactly
拍摄收益不高或不完全
how it works
这个怎么运作
depends on whether
取决于是否
the the they're facing a good or bad
他们面临的是好是坏
suspect and also that determines the
怀疑，这也决定了
strategy of the other player and so
其他玩家的策略等等
there's no strategic uncertainty about
没有战略不确定性
what the other player is going to do
另一位玩家将要做什么
which depends on the state and there's
这取决于国家，
payoff uncertainty about what the best
最佳收益的不确定性
thing to do is for the sheriff based on
要做的是为治安官基于
the state and putting those two things
国家，把这两件事
together we solve we get a basing
我们一起解决，我们得到了基础
equilibrium and we end up making a
平衡，我们最终做出一个
prediction okay so this is a simple game
预测好，所以这是一个简单的游戏
but you know it's going to capture a lot
但是你知道它会吸引很多人
of things in terms of how how players
玩家如何进行游戏
are going to make decisions and
将要做出决定，
uncertain environments and Bayesian
不确定的环境和贝叶斯
equilibrium moves us one step closer to
平衡使我们更接近一步
applications where in many many games in
在许多游戏中的应用
the actual world you have uncertainty in
您在不确定的现实世界中
terms of of what the payoffs are going
收益的条件
to be and what other players are going
以及其他玩家将要做什么
to do so summary of Bayesian Nash
这样做的贝叶斯纳什总结
equilibria what have we got it's it's a
均衡我们得到了什么
model that it explicitly captures on
明确捕获的模型
certain environments and players choose
某些环境和玩家选择
strategies again equilibrium notion so
策略再次达到均衡概念
you're maximizing your payoffs in
您在最大化您的回报
response to uncertainty about both how
对不确定性的回应
other individuals are going to play and
其他人要去玩，
what the payoffs are from from different
来自不同方面的收益
actions so it's a very powerful tool and
动作，所以它是一个非常强大的工具，
one that has many applications some of
具有许多应用程序的一些
which we'll see in some of the added
我们会在一些添加的内容中看到
lectures take care
讲座要照顾